https://soccerstore.com/shop/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). Please read on if you wish to learn more about our privacy policy.
What Information do we collect?
We keep only the information about how you have navigated our website. We temporarily keep information on the products you have added to your basket. We do not keep any personal information that would identify you in the future. When processing your order at Amazon there are other details that will be required - see the relevant Amazon Privacy Policy for full details.
We also record usage data such as the pages visited. This information is completely anonymous.
If you sign up for our Newsletter, we will ask for your email address. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time.
How do we protect your information?
Any information we hold is secured in accordance with our internal security policy.
Do we use cookies?
We use cookies to enable you to hold the content of your shopping basket between visits and to record anonymous traffic data. We do not store any personally identifying information in these cookies.
Will we sell your information?
We do not sell any information about their customers; as simple as that. We will not forward your details on to any third party at any time.
European Clubs
Ajax Amsterdam ( 176
)
Celtic ( 175
)
Rangers ( 185
)
Juventus ( 223
)
Inter Milan ( 237
)
AC Milan ( 235
)
Napoli ( 163
)
Real Madrid ( 241
)
Barcelona ( 243
)
Ronaldo ( 178
)
Black Friday and Cyber Monday Deals ( 17
)
Messi ( 184
)
Hooked ( 10
)
All Products
English Clubs
Arsenal ( 219
)
Liverpool ( 141
)
Manchester City ( 266
)
Leicester City ( 197
)
Chelsea ( 207
)
Manchester United ( 268
)
Tottenham Hotspur ( 216
)
West Ham ( 220
)
Newcastle ( 233
)
All Products
Soccer Shoes
Adidas Soccer Shoes ( 205
)
Nike Soccer Shoes ( 285
)
Puma Soccer Shoes ( 238
)
Cookies help us deliver our services. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies.
Learn More
Accept
Wait! We have a something for you...
Don't leave empty-handed! Simply enter your email below and we will send you a great discount on our products:
We hate spam as much as you do! Your details are never shared and you can unsubscribe at any time.
no thanks
